SELCUK SASOGLU

SOFTWARE ENGINEER / TECHNICAL LEADER

PROFILE

I have been working on software since 2006. My career started in defense industry as a software test engineer and after two years I started doing the job that I am passionate about. Since 2008 I have participated in many projects, developing software for leading IT companies.

EDUCATION

GAZI UNIVERSITY

2007 - 2010, Turkey Master of Science in **Electrical and Electronics** Engineering

GAZI UNIVERSITY

2001 - 2005, Turkey Bachelors Degree in **Electrical and Electronics** Engineering

CONTACT

Nootdorp, Netherlands **Q**



selcuk.sasoglu@gmail.com



https://www.selcuksasoglu.com 🛖



ssasoglu in

INTERESTS

Photography Reading **Boxing** Gaming Music

EXPERIENCE

EXACT CLOUD DEVELOPMENT B.V.

2016 - Present

Senior Software Engineer, Technical Team Leader

I worked as a full-stack engineer for cloud development projects in Exact. I participated in development of the REST API for mobile only accountancy software targeting micro businesses. We worked as a lean-startup within the enterprise in a multidisciplinary team where all decisions were made in a datadriven fashion. I created the cloud architecture from scratch on Azure as the tech lead of the international team. I started working initially on back-end and later on switched to mobile development of the project.

Azure Cloud ASP.NET REST .NET React Redux React-Native C# Javascript Functional Programming Onion Architecture Continuous Integration

Continuous Delivery NoSQL CosmosDB Azure Search Azure Blob Storage

Azure Notification Hub Domain Driven Design Automated Tests

Behavior Driven Development

GATE ELECTRONIC

2014-2016

Technical Team Leader

I worked as technical team leader of a small team for national Public Procurement Platform of Turkey (EKAP). My team was mostly responsible for back-end development where I also worked as a research engineer to try new technologies that can be used on the platform for better user experience. The project team was transfered from Fujitsu Technology Solutions to Gate Electronic at 2014 after a procurement.

Service Oriented Architecture Elasticsearch Logstash Kibana ELK Stack Solr REST SQL .NET C# NoSQL Lucene.NET ASP.NET WCF WPF Ranorex Behavior Driven Development Automated Tests Digital Signatures

FUJITSU TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS



ekap

ekap

2011 - 2014

Senior Software Engineer

I was responsible for design, development and maintenance of integration module on national Public Procurement Platform of Turkey (EKAP).

Service Oriented Architecture SQL NET C# ASP.NET WCF XAdEs-T Digital Signatures

SIEMENS ENTERPRISE COMMUNICATIONS



2008 - 2011

Software Engineer

I was responsible for design, development and maintenance of integration module on national Public Procurement Platform of Turkey (EKAP).

Service Oriented Architecture SQL .NET C# ASP.NET WCF Java Crystal Reports

MS Office

AYESAS

2006 - 2008

Software Engineer

I worked as software test engineer for the military project RADNET and aviation project SmartDeck.

C++ Black box testing Custom tools DO-178B